iglomovies.com 2015-03-17

# Privacy Policy / Terms of Service | IGLO Movies

**Personal identification information

We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, fill out a form, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, email address. Users may, however, visit our Site anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.

Non-personal identification information

We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.

Web browser cookies

Our Site may use "cookies" to enhance User experience. User's web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.

How we use collected information

IGLO Movies may collect and use Users personal information for the following purposes:  
\- To improve customer service  
Information you provide helps us respond to your customer service requests and support needs more efficiently.  
\- To improve our Site  
We may use feedback you provide to improve our products and services.  
\- To send periodic emails  
We may use the email address to respond to their inquiries, questions, and/or other requests. If User decides to opt-in to our mailing list, they will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. If at any time the User would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, they may do so by contacting us via our Site.  
How we protect your information

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site.

Sensitive and private data exchange between the Site and its Users happens over a SSL secured communication channel and is encrypted and protected with digital signatures.

Sharing your personal information

We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above.

Third party websites

Users may find advertising or other content on our Site that link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Site. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our Site, is subject to that website's own terms and policies.

Advertising

Ads appearing on our site may be delivered to Users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile non personal identification information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This privacy policy does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

Terms of Service / Guidelines

The IGLO Movies website complies with all current laws and requirements and will adhere and abide by any formal request from authorities to remove any specified content. IGLO Movies does not host, upload or distribute any copyright material and only provides  links to other websites that host relating content. Please Contact Us with any suspected copyrighted images/material if hosted on our website's server and/or any third party links that might host any such content. Links to third party websites that are suspected of hosting illegal content or material will be removed immediately. Please note that the IGLO Movies website does not offer any form of subscription and or service other then providing links to third party websites that might host relating content. The IGLO Movies website is not responsible for any activity or actions taken once visiting any third party website through advertisements or links found on our website. The IGLO Movies website would like to strongly encourage all our visitors to support the makers of movies and notify us immediately of any suspected illegal content or material when found on any of the third party websites that IGLO Movies links to.

Changes to this privacy policy

IGLO Movies has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

Your acceptance of these terms

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy and terms of service. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

Contacting us:

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us at:  
IGLO Movies Contact Form

This document was last updated on Monday March 8, 2015

**
